

# Producer / Project Manager



acjh13.github.io







Highly adaptive and multi-disciplined Producer / Project Manager with a technical and design background. Experienced in leading interdisciplinary teams in fast-paced environments. Keen eye for quality and risk assessment. Passionate about elevating teams to excellence by ensuring smooth processes and pipelines.

# **Industry Experience**

Junior Producer | Lionfish Studios Pte Ltd – Multiple Projects Mar 2021 - Present

- Managing communications between development team and stakeholders
- Managing in-house and outsourced development teams across 5 projects
- Overseeing project milestones and releases
- Coordinating project development with multiple cross-functional teams
- Leading company-wide transition to a Sprint-based development cycle

**Production Intern** | gumi Asia Pte Ltd - Final Fantasy Brave Exvius Sept 2020 - Feb 2021

- Responsible for Design team's Sprint Planning and follow ups with Jira
- Maintained event lists for content updates with Google Sheets and Confluence
- Assisted Associate Producer in integrating new ticketing workflow
- Began department-wide initiative to streamline and automate workflows
  - Reduced Jira ticket creation / modification time by 50%

# On-Campus Experience

**Teaching Assistant** | DigiPen Singapore – Game Production Class Sept 2019 - Mar 2020

Advised ~10 student teams on project management and game production

# **Academic Projects**

### **Producer, Editor Programmer, Cinematics Designer**

Kindred | Sept 2019 – June 2020, 35 Weeks | 11 Person Team

- 3D narrative game developed on a custom C++ engine and editor with C# scripting
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- Communicated game's direction across team members and lecturers
- Adopted Agile methodology with weekly Scrum meetings and Kanban boards
- Created cross-department workflows for better communication
- Finalist in multiple categories, DigiPen Game Awards 2020

## **Producer, Engine & Editor Programmer**

Mega Macho Brothers | Sept 2018 – Apr 2019, 30 Weeks | 7 Person Team

- 2D co-op action platformer developed on a custom C++ engine and editor
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- Worked with lecturers and team members to resolve conflicts
- Awarded Unity Best Sophomore Game, DigiPen Game Awards 2019

## Education

# Bachelor of Science in **Computer Science and Game Design**

DigiPen Institute of Technology, Singapore Sept 2017 - Apr 2021

- Dean's Honour List, Fall '19
- Exchange Student DigiPen Redmond, Summer '19

### Certifications

### Certified ScrumMaster (CSM)

Scrum Alliance, July 2021

## Skills

#### **Soft Skills**

**Effective Communication Team Management Detail Oriented Problem Solving Conflict Resolution Project Ownership** 

### **Management Methods**

Agile Scrum Kanban

### **Management Software**

Jira Trello Confluence HacknPlan Discord Slack Google Suite Microsoft Suite

#### **Software & Tools**

Git / SVN Microsoft Office Visual Studio Visual Studio Code Unity **Unreal Engine** Custom Game Engine(s) Zapier

#### **Programming Languages**

C / C++ C# Python JavaScript Rust Lua

#### **Spoken Languages**

English Mandarin

For more details on my projects, see my Portfolio!